여기 봐! 조이 사진이야
진짜 주연인가 봐
Oh, look! There's Joey's picture!
This is so exciting!
You can spot someone who's
never seen his plays.
녀석의 출연작을 보지 않고
섣불리 기대하지마
녀석의 연기는 언제나
나의 예상을 뒤엎었어
Notice, no fear.
No sense of impending doom.
"The role of man number three
will not be played by Vic Shapiro. "
3번의 배역은 샤피로가 아님
오늘 잘못 온 것 같다
We came on the wrong night.
잡지라도 가져올걸
I can't believe I forgot a magazine.
그만들 해, 재밌을지도 몰라
-Come on, this might be good.
-I don't know.
제목부터 심상치 않아
The exclamation point scares me.
It's not just Freud, it's Freud!
그냥 '프로이트'가 아니라
'프로이트! '야
쉬! 연극이 시작된다
Magic is about to happen!
Well, Eva...
에바, 그간 치료를
훌륭히 잘 받았소
...we've done
some excellent work here.
이제, 당신의 문제를
분명하게 파악했어요
And I would have to say...
...your problem is quite clear.
All you want is a dinkle
당신이 원하는 건
남자의 상징!
그걸로 뭘 하려고?
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
그건 그저 쉬할 때나 쓰는 것
제길, 대체 그딴 건 왜 원해
To play with or simply let hang
The One With the Butt
모욕당한 기분이야
I feel violated.
Did anybody else feel like
peeling their skin off...
배우들의 살갗이 홀랑 벗겨지는
느낌이 들진 않았어?
...to have something else to do?
- 로스, 10시다
- 그래? 기분은 새벽 2시다
Ross, 1 0:00.
Is it? It feels like 2.
-No, 1 0:00!
-What?
- 아니, 10시!
- 뭐?
아름다운 여인이
8, 9, 10시 방향에 있어
There's a beautiful woman
at 8, 9, 1 0:00!
Hello!
이런!
너무 매혹적이야!
She's amazing! She makes the women l
dream about look like fat, bald men.
나 자신이 뚱뚱이 대머리가
된 것처럼 자신감이 없어져
Go over.
She's not with anyone.
가봐, 혼자인 거 같은데
가서 첫 대사를 뭘로 할까?
실례합니다...
And what would my opening line be?
Excuse me....
Come on, she's a person.
You can do it.
저 여자도 인간이야
가봐
내 수준에 맞는 여자일까?
로스, 도와줘
Could she be more out of my league?
Back me up.
그런 식으로 하다간
백년이 가도 힘들지
He couldn't get a woman
like that in a million years.
고맙네, 친구
예쁜 여자가 못난 남자를
선택하는 경우도 있어
You always see these beautiful
women with "nothing" guys.
You could be one of those guys.
그러니 너도 가능해
-You could do that.
-You think?
그래, 할 수 있어
- 그래?
- 그래, 확신해
Absolutely!
시도해볼 생각 자체가 무모해
혀가 잘 돌아갈까 몰라
I can't believe
I'm considering this.
-l' m very aware of my tongue.
-Come on.
- 어서 가봐
- 그래, 간다
Here goes.
약간 물러서라
독설의 파편이 튈라
Stand back, everyone.
Incoming ego shrapnel.
All right, I can do this.
난 할 수 있다
-Yes?
-Hi.
뭐죠?
안녕하세요?
다음 말은...
Okay, next word would be...
챈들러...
그게 내 이름이에요
... Chandler.
Chandler is my name and....
Hi!
안녕하세요?
Yes, you said that.
인사는 했는데요
네, 벌써 했죠
Yes! Yes, I did.
But what I didn't say....
제가 하지 않은 말은...
제가 하고 싶은 말은...
What I wanted to say was...
시간 내주시면 고마울 거고
잘 가세요
...would you like to go out with me?
Thank you. Good night.
챈들러?
Chandler?
- 야, 정말...
- 정말...
- 너 춤 잘 추더라
- 연기를 하다니...
-I didn't know you could dance!
-You were in a play!
- 수염이 없네
- 어땠어?
What'd you think?
-I didn't know you could dance!
-You were in a play!
- 너 춤 잘 추더라
- 연기를 하다니...
수염이 없네
그만들 해, 그렇게 엉망은 아냐
내가 주연이었어!
It wasn't that bad.
I was the lead.
It was better than the troll thing.
At least you got to see my head.
춤과 노래는 더 나았어
내 머리를 보면 알잖아
- 그래, 맞아
- 머리를 봤어
-You're right.
-We saw your head.
내 독일 억양도 죽였지?
How about that accent?
그래, 무조건 침만 튀더라
Yeah. All of your W's were V's.
좋대, 좋대!
She said yes!
끔찍한 연극이었어, 친구!
Awful play, man!
Her name's Aurora. She's ltalian
and she pronounces my name " Chandler. "
이름은 오로라, 이태리 억양으로
날 이렇게 불렀어 "챈들러!"
I like that better.
앞으로 그렇게 불러 줘
극장 감독이 너한테
전해주래
The usher gave me this.
- 뭐야?
- 배우 에이전시의 에스텔!
-What is it?
-The Estelle Leonard T alent Agency.
에이전시에서 명함을 남겼어
계약이라도 할 건가봐
An agency left its card.
They wanna sign me!
이 연극을 봤대?
Based on this play?
이 연극을 봤구나!
Based on this play!
Look! There's a note on the back.
여기, 뒤에 메모가 있어
연기 좋았어요
활력이 넘칩니다
"Loved your work. Call me a sap. "
꽤 감동했나봐
She was obviously very moved!
You should call her fairly quickly.
감동을 잊기 전에
빨리 연락해
응, 당장 할거야
Yeah! As soon as possible!
들어와요
Come in!
에스텔 레나드 씨?
Hi. I'm here to see Estelle Leonard.
있나 확인해 보구요
Just a moment, let me see
if she's in.
Hello.
어서 와요
-You' re Estelle?
-I know...
- 당신이 에스텔인가요?
- 표정 보니 알겠군
...you weren't expecting someone
so fantastically beautiful.
이런 미인이
에이전트일 줄 몰랐죠?
청년, 안심해요
앉아요, 어서요
Love lump. T ake a load off already,
darling. Sit already.
여기 온 것만으로도
대단히 기쁩니다
I can't tell you how excited
I am to be here.
당연하지
Why not?
- 그러니까, 제 말은...
- 대화 중에 식사해도 괜찮죠?
-What I meant was
-You don't mind if I eat, do you?
괜찮아요
조이, 뭐 하나 물읍시다
Joey...
...sweetheart, let me ask you
a question.
Did you ever see the movie
Sleepless in Seattle?
'시애틀의 잠 못
이루는 밤'을 봤소?
네, 그 배우들이 여기 소속이에요?
-Wow! Do you represent those actors?
-No.
아뇨, 그 영화 마지막 장면의
해피엔딩 기억나죠?
But you know the end,
where they' re happy?
That's gonna be you and me.
그게 바로 당신과 나요
저와 계약하실 건가요?
You mean you wanna sign me?
아니, 엠파이어스테이트
빌딩에나 가 봅시다
No, I wanna go to the top of the
Empire State Building and make out.
물론 계약할 거요
Of course I wanna sign you!
에스텔...
이런, 죄송합니다
-Miss Leonard, I'm so
-Oh, boy.
- 조심해야지
- 죄송합니다
-Ride them, cowboy.
-l' m sorry!
매직아이
I don't see it!
안 보여
그림이 안 올라와
그냥 지나쳐 봐
-T ry to look through it.
-Unfocus your eyes.
응, 초점을 맞추지마
어차피 초점을 맞출
그림도 없어
Focus? There's nothing to focus on.
-It's the Statue of Liberty!
-Right!
- 자유의 여신상이다!
- 그래?
뭐? 여신상이 어딨어?
-Where's the Statue of Liberty?
-There.
바로 거기!
난 여기서도 보인다
I can't not see it now.
- 나 왔다
- 안녕, 챈들러
Hey, kids!
Come here. Do you see anything here?
너 여기 뭐 보이니?
응, 보트
-lt looks like a boat.
-A boat.
보트!
- 응, 자유의 여신상 앞에
- 이런!
Right in front of
the Statue of Liberty.
들어온 지 7초나 지났는데
데이트가 어땠는지 안 궁금해?
It's been seven seconds, and you
haven't asked me how my date went.
- 참, 그래
- 데이트 어땠어, 챈들러?
How was your date, Chandler?
It was unbelievable!
정말 끝내줬어!
이런 여자는 처음이야
인생 자체가 놀라워
I've never met anyone like her.
She's had an amazing life!
She was in the Israeli army.
이스라엘 군대에 있었대...
다행히, 총알이 엔진을 비켜가서
무사하게 국경에 닿았죠
None of the bullets hit the engine,
so we made it to the border.
그리고 간신히...
너무 제 얘기만 떠들었네요
But just barely, and l....
I've been talking about myself
all night long. I'm sorry.
미안해요, 당신은 어때요?
사는 얘기 좀 해봐요
What about you? T ell me a story.
All right, once...
일전에...
일전에, 지하철을 탔어요
... I got on the subway.
And it was at night...
밤이었는데,
브룩클린까지 타고 갔죠
...and I rode it all the way
to Brooklyn.
Just for the hell of it.
이게 바로 제 삶이에요
대화가 계속 이어졌어
정말 완벽한 오후였지
We talked until 2:00. It was perfect.
More or less.
우리가 예멘 땅에 있다는 걸
깨달았죠
Suddenly, we realized we were
in Yemen.
I' m sorry, so "we" is...?
미안하지만, 우리가...?
저와 릭이요
"We" is me and Rick.
Who's Rick?
릭이 누구야?
릭이 누구죠?
Who's Rick?
My husband.
남편이요
그럼 이혼했나요?
-Oh, so you' re divorced?
-No.
아뇨
미안하지만, 미망인?
바라옵건데...
I' m sorry. So you' re widowed?
Hopefully?
아뇨, 전 기혼자예요
No, l' m still married.
그럼 당신 남편이 여기있는
당신에게 뭐라고 할까요?
So, how would your husband feel
about you sitting here with me...
당신이 발가락으로 내 주머니의
동전을 세는 모습이요
...sliding your foot so far up my leg
you can count the change in my pocket?
Don't worry.
걱정 말아요
별일 없을 거예요
이던도 이해하거든요
He'd be okay with you
because he's okay with Ethan.
이던?
이던이라고요?
Ethan? There's an Ethan?
Ethan is my boyfriend.
이던은...
제 애인이에요
What?
뭐?
What kind of relationship
do you imagine us having...
설명 좀 해주시죠
우리 관계는 어떤 건가요?
남편과 애인도 있으신 분인데
...if you have a husband
and a boyfriend?
성적 파트너겠죠
I suppose, mainly sexual.
그렇게 돼서, 안 됐다
Sorry it didn't work out.
What, not work out?
I'm seeing her again on Thursday.
안 되다니?
또 만날 건데
Didn't you listen to the story?
내 얘길 잘 들은 거야?
Didn't you listen? It's twisted!
내 말은 못 들은 거야?
그건 부정한 짓이야
어떻게 그런 여자를 또 만나?
How could you get involved
with her?
물론 처음엔 나도 고민했지
하지만 좋은 면만 보기로 했어
I had trouble with it at first.
But I get the good stuff.
재밌고, 대화 좋고, 섹스 좋고
게다가 책임질 필요도 없지
All the fun, all the talking,
all the sex...
...and none of the responsibility.
이건 모든 남자들의
꿈이라구!
-This is every guy's fantasy!
-That's not true!
그렇지 않아
-Ross, is this your fantasy?
-No, of course not.
- 로스, 네 꿈도 저거야?
- 아니, 절대 아냐
응, 사실 그래
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
남자들은 딴 남자 만나는
여자를 개의치 않는다는 거야?
You'd go out with someone
going out with someone else?
-I couldn't.
-Good for you.
- 난 싫어
- 다행이야
When l' m with a woman,
I need to know...
난 여자를 만날 때 나보다
애인이 더 많은 건 질색이야
... I' m going out
with more people than her.
Once, I went out with a guy who
just got divorced.
나도 이혼한 남자를 만났었는데
정말 힘들었어
It was hard. His kids liked me
better than him.
애들이 나를 더 좋아했거든
그게 챈들러 일과
무슨 상관이 있어?
What does this have to do
with Chandler?
없어
Nothing.
저런 주제는 처음이라서
다른 걸 꺼내봤어
I didn't have anything
on that topic.
So I went another way.
You know, monogamy can be
a tricky concept.
일부일처만이... 진리는 아냐
인류학적으로 볼 때...
I mean, anthropologically speaking
Fine. Now you'll never know.
알았어, 너희는 몰라도 된다
We' re kidding. T ell us.
- 장난이야, 말해봐
- 우리도 알고 싶어
-We wanna know.
-Come on!
좋아, 리차드 리키라는
학자의 이론에 따르면...
All right. There's a theory
put forth by Richard Leakey
짜잔!
Are we greeting each other
this way now? I like it.
이제부터 그렇게 인사할래?
아주 좋아
내가 청소했어
창문도 닦고, 바닥도 쓸고
Look! I cleaned!
I did the windows.
I did the floors.
진공청소기도 조립했고...
I used all the vacuum attachments but
the round one. What's it for?
솔이 달린 둥그런 건
뭔지 몰라서 못 썼어
원래 아는 사람도 없고
묻지도 않아
Nobody knows.
And we're not supposed to ask.
어떤 거 같아?
What do you think?
-It's very clean.
-Really, it looks great!
- 깨끗하네
- 잘했어, 정말 잘했어!
I see you moved the green ottoman.
녹색 발판을 옮겼네
How did that happen?
어떻게 된 거야?
I don't know. It looked better there.
저기 있는 게
나을 것 같아서 옮겼어
탁자 옆에 의자가
하나 더 생겼잖아
And it's an extra seat
around the table.
Yeah, it's interesting.
좋은 발상이야
이러면 어떨까? 재미 삼아...
옛날에 있던 자리로 옮기고...
But you know what? Just for fun...
...Iet's see what it looked like
in the old spot.
비교 해보자!
Just to compare.
Let's see.
어디... 봐! 여기도 좋다
그냥 여기 두기로 하자
Well, it looks good there too.
Let's leave it there for a while.
감히 저 발판을 옮길
생각을 하다니
I can't believe you moved
the green ottoman.
잡지책을 내놓지
않은 게 다행이야
Be glad you didn't fan the magazines.
She'll scratch your eyes out.
그걸로 네 머리를
칠 수도 있거든
- 난 그렇게 못되지 않았어!
- 너 되게 못됐어
-You guys, I am not that bad!
-Yeah, you are.
Remember, I lived with you?
You were a little....
나랑 살 때 기억나?
넌 매일 이랬어
내가 언제 그랬어?
That is so unfair!
우리가 어렸을 적에
네 인형은 늘 새 거였어
When we were kids, yours was the only
Raggedy Ann doll that wasn't raggedy.
안 그럼 난리가 나니까
Okay, so I'm responsible.
I'm organized.
좋아, 난 꼼꼼하고 세심해
그래, 난 괴짜야!
But hey, I can be a kook!
All right, you madcap gal!
그래, 말괄량이야!
Imagine this.
이걸 상상해봐
The phone bill arrives,
but you don't pay it right away.
요금 고지서가 와도
넌 바로 안 내
-Why not?
-Because you're a kook!
왜?
넌 괴짜니까!
경고장이 올 때까지
기다리는 거야
You wait until they send a notice.
I could do that.
그럴 수도 있지
나보고 쇼핑하라고 시켜서
Okay, then you let me
go grocery shopping
-No problem.
-I'm not done yet.
- 그거야 좋지
- 이제 시작이야
세제를 사왔는데
세제통 구멍이 크지 않다면?
And I buy detergent, but it's not
the one with the easy-pour spout.
그걸 뭐 하러 사와?
Why would someone do that?
One might wonder.
다 그렇지 않아?
난 상관 안 할걸
But I would be fine with that.
누군가 탁자에 받침도 없이
컵을 놨어
A glass is on the table with no
coaster. A cold drink. A hot day.
더운 날이라
그 안에 얼음이 들어있어
작은 물방울들이 응집되어
조금씩 나무 탁자에 스며들어...
Beads of condensation are inching
closer to the wood....
Stop it!
그만해!
세상에! 맞아
내가 왜 그러지?
Oh, my God!
It's true. Who am l?
모니카?
Monica, you' re Mom.
넌 엄마 같아
네, 네, 정말요?
Oh, my God!
좋아요, 제가 할게요
Okay, I'll be there.
That was my agent.
내 에이전트야
에이전트 말이 내가...
알 파치노 영화에 출연한대
My agent has just gotten me a job
in the new Al Pacino movie!
- 잘 됐다
- 세상에!
-That's great!
-What's the part?
무슨 역할인데?
믿겨져? 알 파치노래!
Can you believe it? Pacino!
This guy's why I became an actor!
그분 때문에
내가 배우를 꿈꿨어
"난 쓰레기요, 당신들도 쓰레기요
이 법정도 쓰레기요!"
" Out of order? You' re out of order!
This whole courtroom's out of order! "
Seriously, what's the part?
진정하고, 역할이 뭐래?
"내가 관뒀다고 생각하면
난 다시 끌려와 있소"
"Just when I thought I was out,
they pull me back in! "
Come on. Seriously, Joey,
what's the part?
그만하고, 배역이 뭐래?
You' re.... What?
역할이... 뭐?
I' m his butt double, okay?
엉덩이 대역이래
I play Al Pacino's butt.
내가 알 파치노의 엉덩이야!
All right? He goes into the shower,
and then...
그분이 욕실에 들어가고
내 엉덩이가 나오는 거야
... I' m his butt.
Oh, my God!
맙소사!
Come on, you guys.
뭐가 어때서?
It's a real Pacino movie
and that's big!
이건 진짜 영화야
알 파치노가 나와
- 거물이잖아!
- 정말 좋겠다
It's terrific. You deserve this.
드디어 성과가 나오는구나
몇 년간 그렇게 고생하더니
After years of struggling you've
cracked your way into show business.
결국, 헐리우드에
엉덩이로 인사하냐?
그래, 실컷 놀려라
상관 안 해, 큰 기회니까
Fine. Make jokes, I don't care.
-This is a big break for me!
-You' re right. It is.
- 네 말이 맞아
- 맞아
그럼 시사회 때
모두 초대할 거지?
So, will you invite us
to the big opening?
나가요
-I need some moisturizer.
-For what?
- 받아, 영양크림 좀 빌려줘
- 왜?
잊었어?
오늘이 촬영이야
T oday's the big day!
족집게는 있니?
거기 털이 좀 나서
You got any tweezers? I think
I have a rogue hair.
God. Go in the bathroom.
Use whatever you want.
욕실에 있는 거 다 써
제발 어디에 발랐는지만
말하지마
Don't ever tell me what you did
in there.
고마워!
Thank you.
-Joey's mom's on the phone.
-ln the bathroom.
조이 집에서 전화 왔어
욕실에 있어
- 지금 들어가지마
- 우린 동거인이야
-You don't wanna go in there!
-Come on, we' re roommates.
My eyes! My eyes!
내 눈! 내 눈!
경고했지?
I warned you.
아침부터 누구야?
Who is being loud?
Oh, that would be Monica.
모니카 비명이야
요리 재료 좀 부탁해
오로라에게 아침을 해주고 싶어
Can I borrow stuff?
I wanna make Aurora breakfast.
밤에 같이 있었어?
You got the whole night?
응, 20분밖에 없어
이던이...
Well, I only have 20 minutes
until Ethan, so....
정말 조금도 화가 안 나?
Do I sense resentment?
No. No resentment. Believe me...
아니, 절대 화 안 나
진심이야, 가치가 있지
...it's worth it, okay?
평생토록 서로에게 중요한 순간을
만들어주는 관계가 어떤지 알아?
In a relationship, you have moments
you'll remember the rest of your life.
오로라와는 매 순간이 좋아
Every single second is like that
with Aurora.
I've just wasted 35 of them
talking to you.
너희랑 노닥거리느라
35초나 낭비했어
So, Monica, can you
help me with the door?
- 모니카 문 좀 열어 줘
- 응
예전의 난 프라이팬을
플라스틱 솔로 문질렀지만...
The old Monica would remind you...
...to scrub that T eflon pan with
a plastic brush.
But l' m not gonna do that.
이젠 그렇게 안 해
난방장치 좀 부탁해요
엉덩이에 소름 돋을까봐요
Excuse me? Can they warm it up?
I' m concerned about goose bumps.
다들 준비됐지?
Everybody ready?
I wanna thank you
for this opportunity.
좋은 기회를 주신
감독님께 감사드립니다
이제 겨우 첫발이지만
언젠가는...
I mean, I know this is just a first
step, but I hope that someday
가운 벗어
Lose the robe.
Right. Okay. Losing the robe!
네, 이제 벗습니다
다 벗었습니다
Okay, and the robe is lost.
I would like to get this in one take.
여러분, 한번에 갑시다
부탁이요
Let's roll it.
카메라 돌고, 물 뿌리고...
Water's working.
액션!
And action!
And cut!
컷!
Butt guy, what are you doing?
엉덩이 친구!
대체 뭐야?
샤워중이죠
I'm showering.
No, that was clenching.
아니, 너무 굳었어
The way I see it,
the guy's upset here, you know?
제가 보기엔 이 남자가
분노하고 있어요
His wife's dead,
his brother's missing.
아내는 죽고,
동생도 실종돼서...
I think his butt would be angry here.
그의 엉덩이도
분노로 굳어졌죠
I think his butt would like
to get the shot before lunch.
그의 엉덩이는 점심 전에
촬영을 끝내고 싶어해
Once again, rolling.
Water working.
다시! 카메라 돌고
물 뿌리고...
And action!
액션!
And cut! What was that?
컷!
그건 뭐요?
I was going for quiet desperation.
절망을 잔잔하게 표현했죠
But if you have to ask....
감독님이 싫으시다면...
God, I love these fingers.
- 손가락이 너무 좋아
- 고마워
Thank you.
No, actually, I meant my fingers.
아니, 내 손가락
Look at them.
Look at how happy they are.
내 손가락이 호강하고 있잖아
-Oh, my God, l' m late!
-Oh, no!
- 이런, 늦었네!
- 안돼, 안돼!
-Don't go.
-Okay.
가지마, 가지마!
그래, 그래
-I have to.
-Look, she's leaving.
- 안돼, 가야돼
- 기어코 가겠다는군
I' m sorry. He'll be waiting for me.
미안해
많이 기다릴 거야
-I thought you talked to Rick.
-It's not Rick.
릭에게 벌써 말했잖아
릭이 아냐
Ethan? He gets the whole day!
이던과는 낮에
종일 붙어있잖아
No, it's Andrew.
아니, 앤드류야
I know there'll be moments...
여태껏 살면서 이렇게 같은
질문을 반복하는 건 처음인데
...when I'll regret asking
the following question, but....
-And Andrew is?
-He's...
- 앤드류는 누구야?
- 새로운 친구
... new.
So you' re not completely fulfilled
by Rick, Ethan and myself?
정말 만족을 못하는군
릭, 이던, 나도 있는데
그런 식으로 말하지마
No, that's not exactly what I was
다른 여자 같으면
좋아 죽었어
Most women would kill...
...for three guys like us.
나 같은 남자가 셋인데
-So, what do you want?
-You.
바라는 게 뭐야?
- 당신!
- 이미 가졌잖아
-You have me.
-No. Just you.
오직 당신만!
-What do you mean?
-Lose the other guys.
무슨 뜻이야?
다른 놈들을 버려
전부 다?
Like, all of them?
나랑 있는 거 좋으면서
왜 안돼?
Come on, we' re great together.
Why not?
Can't we have what we have now?
현재 관계만 유지할 순 없어?
Why can't we talk and make love...
대화하고, 웃고, 사랑하고
서로에게 의무감도 없고 말야
...without feeling obligated
to each other?
Up until tonight, I thought
that's what you wanted too.
방금 전만 해도 당신도
그런 걸 원했잖아
Well, part of me wants that...
그런 생각도 내 일부지
내 속에 다른 내가 있어
... but it's like l' m two guys.
One guy's saying, "This is great! "
한 녀석은
닥쳐, 지금이 좋아
딴 녀석도 있어
But there's this other guy.
이 녀석은 한껏 기분이 부풀었는데
그걸 제어할 장치를 잃어버렸어
The guy who wells up
when the Grinch's heart grows...
...and breaks that measuring device.
He's saying, you know,
"This is too hard. Get out! "
"이건 너무 힘들어
관둬, 관둬!" 이래
So, which one of the guys
will you listen to?
둘 중에, 어떤 소리를 듣지?
I have to listen to both.
They don't let each other finish.
몰라, 둘 다 들어야지
서로 계속 싸우고 있거든
Which one?
선택해
The second guy.
두 번째
I see.
그래?
맘 바뀌면 전화해
Call me if you change your mind.
Sorry, the first guy runs the lips.
미안해, 첫 번째 녀석이
튀어나왔어
이렇게 생각해
Look at it this way. You dumped her!
- 네가 차버린 거야
- 그래
Right? I mean, this woman was
unbelievably sexy...
이 여자는 너무 섹시하고
아름답고, 지적이고
못 올라갈 나무지
...and beautiful, intelligent,
unattainable.
T ell me why you did this again?
왜 헤어진 거니?
왔구나!
- 안녕! 스타 양반
- 오셨다!
Movie star!
혹시 알 파치노 영화의
연기파 엉덩이님 아니세요?
Wait! Aren't you the guy who plays
the butt in the new Pacino movie?
Nope.
아니
No? What happened, big guy?
아냐?
왜 그래, 거물?
거물?
Big guy?
It felt like a "big guy" moment.
거물이라고 느꼈었지
잘렸어!
I got fired!
내 연기가 너무 오버한데
They said I acted too much with it.
I told everybody about this!
소문은 있는 대로 내서
다들 극장에 갈텐데...
-Everybody's expecting to see me.
-lKnow what?
그게 누구 엉덩이인줄
모를 거야
-No one will be able to tell.
-My mom will.
우리 엄만 알지
아주 다정하고도
혼란스런 엉덩이지
There's something so sweet
and disturbing about that.
I've done crappy plays
for six years...
6년간 엉터리 연기만 하다가
겨우 한 컷을 얻었는데
...and I finally get my shot,
and I blow it!
망쳐버렸어!
그건 네 컷이 아냐
Maybe this wasn't it.
그래, 네 컷이라면
네 스스로가 알지
I think when it's your shot,
you know it's your shot.
Did it feel like your shot?
그게 네 컷으로 느껴졌어?
Hard to tell. I was naked.
몰라, 벗은 거 외에는
I don't think this was it.
I don't think you just get one.
네 컷은 아닌 것 같아
큰 장면도 아니고 컷이잖아
I believe things are gonna happen
for you. I do.
언젠간 진짜 너를 위한
장면이 얻어질 거야, 진짜야
You've got to think about
the day some kid will go:
이런 날을 상상해봐
어떤 신인배우가 친구에게
"배역이 왔어, 역할이!
조이 트리비아니의 엉덩이래!"
"l got the part!
I'm gonna be Joey T ribbiani's ass! "
그럴까? 고맙다
You think? That's so nice.
우리도
I' m sorry, Joey.
I' m gonna go to bed, guys.
안 됐어, 조이
난 이만 잘게
- 잘 자
-Good night.
모니카, 신발을 여기
놓고 갈거니?
You' re gonna leave
your shoes out here?
정말이야?
Really? Just casually
strewn about...
이렇게 무방비 상태로
아무렇게나 둬도 돼?
...in that reckless, haphazard manner?
It doesn't matter.
I'll get them tomorrow. Or not!
신경 안 써
내일 챙길 거야
Whenever.
아무 때나 하지 뭐!
She is a kook.
역시 괴짜란 말야
그렇게 신경 쓰이면
나가서 신발을 가져와
If it bothers you that much,
just go out and get the shoes.
아냐, 그러면 안돼
이건 바보짓이야
No, don 't do this!
This is stupid!
I don 't have to prove anything.
I'm gonna get them.
내가 바뀔 필요는 없어
가서 가져올 거야
그럼 다들 보게 될텐데
But then everyone will know.
아침 일찍 일어나서
방에 갖다 놓자
Unless I get them, then wake up
really early and put them back.
나 정말 왜 이래!
I need help!
당신이 원하는 건...
-All you want is a dinkle
-Not that song!
제발 그만...
-All you envy's a schwang
-Come on, you guys.
남자의 상징!
그걸로 뭘 하려고?
그건 그저 쉬할 때나 쓰는 것
제길, 대체 그딴 건 왜 원해
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang
All you want is a dinkle
당신이 원하는 건
남자의 상징!
What you envy's a schwang
그걸로 뭘 하려고?
그건 그저 쉬할 때나 쓰는 것
제길, 대체 그딴 건 왜 원해
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang